### **CURRICULUM - VITAE**

# Priyanka C. Modi

30 JivarajnagarSociety | Near Police Commissioner Office | Shahibaug | Ahmedabad: 380004.

Cell: 9924851355, 9099967223 | E-mail: priyankapriyankamodi@gmail.com

### **OBJECTIVE**

To obtain a position with a progressive web development or software development company with a strong focus on creativity and problem solving. To support a network infrastructure based on multiple operating systems and complex network topologies. To find a position that is challenging, rewarding and provides an opportunity to expand my knowledge and abilities in creating client centric solutions.

### PERSONAL INFORMATION

Birth Date | 30, January 1986 Nationality | Indian Visa Status | Citizen Marital Status | Single

## **AREA OF INTEREST**

More than 3 years of experience in software development. Created the complex and simple projects including content management, e-commerce, chats, customer relations and communication interfaces. The projects based on PHP in conjunction with various other web development technologies. PHP (Core PHP, PHP with OOP, PHP with frameworks: MVC Framework), SQL (MySQL, Oracle), E-commerce(Magento, Wordpress), JQuery, AJAX, XHTML / HTML, CSS, XML and SEO are used.

I have worked in the following Areas:

- Dynamic content applications
- E-commerce applications
- Content management systems

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Hardware	IBM PC Compatibles; Intel, AMD platform
Software	Adobe Photoshop, Dreamwever, Zend Studio, Gedit Text Editor
Operation Systems/Platforms	Windows98/NT/2000/ 2000 Sever/XP/2003/2003 Server/Vista, Linux/Unix
Tools and Technologies	Core PHP (5, 4 and 3), MySQL, XHTML / HTML / XML, JavaScript, CSS, C, C++, MVC (Model View Controller), SQL, Apache Web Server, Familiarity with many other web technologies (ASP, JSP, ORACLE, ORACLE 9i, SQL Server, MY-SQL Server 2000, MS-Access)
CMS	Joomla, Magento, WordPress

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

**Software Engineer |** May, 2016 - Present, 2016 **Rightway Solution** | Prahladnagar, Ahmedabad, Gujarat

Environment | Core PHP, MYSQL, Magento

## Responsibilities

- Theme Integration on Magento,
- Develop the Custom Module in magento
- Debug the code on custom module and product

### Website

Magento Website | http://www.ohoshop.in/

PHP Web Developer | October, 2013 - April, 2016

iFlair Web Technologies Pvt. Ltd. | Paldi, Ahmedabad, Gujarat

**Environment |** Core PHP, MYSQL, Wordpress, Magento

## Responsibilities

- Theme Integration on Magento, Wordpress
- Develop, Modify and Testing the dynamic website in Magento, Wordpress and Core PHP
- Install the extension for magento and plugin for wordpress as per require for website
- Modify the code for install the extension
- Import and Export the products on magento
- Responsible for analyzing program performance.
- Maintained confidentiality with regard to the information being stored, processed or accessed.

#### Website

**Magento Website** | (http://www.ipsamplecenter.com/, http://www.myelectricradiators.com/, http://makkaya.com/shop/)

Wordpress Website | (http://hindxpress.com/, http://yacht-time.de/,

http://www.walkerprestons.co.uk, http://novacr.com.au/, http://mytekcareer.com,

http://newmillmagazine.com/, http://thecommongroundnetwork.com/,

http://intheblacknet.com/)

PHP Web Developer | October, 2012 - July, 2013

Indylogix Solution | Chankheda, Ahmedabad, Gujarat

**Environment** | Core PHP, MYSQL, Wordpress

## Responsibilities

- Develop, Testing and Modify website on Wordpress.
- Responsible for testing and developing programming modifications in website.
- Responsible for analyzing program performance.
- Maintained confidentiality with regard to the information being stored, processed or accessed.

### Website

**Wordpress Website** | (http://cmax.net.au/, http://cmax.net.au/ (mobile version), http://www.victoriacochrane.com/, http://project.demotestserver.com/new\_wilderness/)

PHP Web Developer | April, 2011 - September, 2012

Kumbh Design Inc. | C.G.Road, Ahmedabad, Gujarat

**Environment** | Core PHP, MYSQL, Wordpress

## Responsibilities

- Assign the tasks of coding, testing and modified program in PHP.
- Responsible for testing and developing programming modifications in website
- Responsible for analyzing program performance.
- Maintained confidentiality with regard to the information being stored, processed or accessed.

### Website

Core PHP Website | (http://www.orbiselevator.com/, http://www.dbscommunities/,

http://www.masstfoods.com/, http://www.roomyexports.com/, http://www.vimalmicrons.com/, http://www.azitra.com)

Wordpress Website | (http://www.nvi.in/, http://www.axisgatepass.com/)

PHP Web Developer / Trainee| August, 2010 - March, 2011

Adit Security System Pvt. Ltd | Shahibaug, Ahmedabad, Gujarat

Environment | Core PHP, Joomla, MYSQL

## Responsibilities

Assign the tasks of coding, testing and modified program by using Joomla in PHP Responsible for testing and developing programming modifications in website Responsible for analyzing program performance

Maintained confidentiality with regard to the information being stored, processed or accessed I have worked in Core PHP for update, delete and add of code in form.

Search Engine Optimization /Junior | January, 2010 - July, 2010

Communication Carft Pvt. Ltd | Mithakhali Cross Roads, Ahmedabad, Gujarat

Environment | SEO – Work on Off-Page Optimization

Responsibilities

As a work on Off-Page Optimization,

- Social Bookmarking
- Compare Link of Google & Yahoo for Social Bookmarking
- Forum Postings
- Directory Submission
- Article Submissions
- Social Media Optimization
- · Press Releases
- Feedback on website for changes

## Website

(http://www.prepaymania.co.uk/, http://www.fones.com/)

# **EDUCATION**

• Master of Science | Computer Application & Information Technology

Gujarat University (K.S.SchoolOf Business Management) | Ahmedabad, Gujarat **Graduation:** June 2008

Bachelor of Science | Computer Application & Information Technology

 $\label{thm:conditional} \textit{Gujarat University (K.S.SchoolOf Business Management)} \mid \textit{Ahmedabad, Gujarat}$ 

**Graduation:** June 2006

# **SPECIALTIES & STRENGTH**

- Nature | Adaptable And Responsible, Sincere
- Strength | Positive Attitude and quick learning ability, Hard worker, Active team Member
- **Weakness** | Impatient To Know The Results, Emotional

# **DECLARATION**

I hereby declare that the above information is correct up to the best of my knowledge and belief.